Every breath, a breakthrough.
Selena Gomez: My Mind & Me is a documentary, music
film directed by Alek Keshishian.
After years in the limelight, Selena Gomez achieves unimaginable stardom.
But just as she reaches a new peak, an unexpected turn pulls her into darkness.
This uniquely raw and intimate documentary spans her
six-year journey into a new light.
Self, played by Selena Gomez.
Self, played by Raquelle Stevens.
Self, played by Ashley Cook.
Self, played by Liana Blackburn.
Self, played by Brent L. Boxberger.
Self, played by Devyck Bull.
Selena Gomez: My Mind & Me is a 2022 American documentary film that follows singer
and actress Selena Gomez during a six year period of her career.
The film documents her struggles with physical and mental well-being in
the wake of her diagnosis with lupus and bipolar disorder.
It was directed by Alek Keshishian, produced by Lighthouse Management + Media and Interscope
Films, and released to Apple TV+ and select theaters on November 4, 2022.
Premiering at the opening night of the AFI Fest on November 2, 2022, Selena Gomez: My Mind & Me was met with
a positive critical reception; the documentary was praised for mental health transparency.
Accompanying the film's release, "My Mind & Me", a song by Gomez
featured in the end credits, was released as a single.
The tone is dark.